OK and so there's the plan i will send you another
proper version of that
but this is entering
the
flat through
D one
and then this
brings us
into room
a
which is the living room
and there we can see
W one
that's the
window
there
and if we take a look around this room you
can
see the computer corner there we've got the back wall
there's the
ceiling and
the
sofa sits in the middle of it
and that's background to
D one
and if we keep coming back around this way
they
can see W one again
and it scans around the room
and then that brings us up to
this door
which is
in room
a
but leaving room a
to enter room C
and this is
D two
so if we go
through there and
what we'll do when we go
through here
is we'll head straight
to
D three
which leads us into the bathroom
which is room B
and this is into the bathroom
this is where i noted that the
height is two two eight of the ceiling
but there's that bit there where the stairs come down over what will be the shower area
so that's something we'll have to incorporate and look at later
if we
walk
through there you
can see that's where the
that brings us up to
D five
and then
behind there's
the toilet
we probably won't have the
D five on the end plans at
the minute the thinking is the toilet 's going to come forward
and
some sort of water boiler is going to go back there
but more on that later this is just to get a layout of the plan
so then go back into room C
and then what's avoid
making confusion here properly is that i've got room C all as one
big open room
and at the minute obviously it's showing as a kitchen and a small bedroom
so the thing is this
small in
in a bedroom here is what is going to be ripped out
so once that is ripped out
room
C will become one big square room
so just for a bit of reference
this is C two
cupboard two
that does run from the floor
to
a certain height
so that's in there
and then we're looking at the
back of the wall
that runs from C two towards C one that's what the camera 's currently looking at
so
if we come back out of here you
can see this wall here that'll be getting taken out it's only a thin
internal wall
very little to
it
and
then we're back
looking
we've got that door there to be aware of
which is D four
that takes you to the
outside
of the flats
via a little shared area
and then we've got
W two
the second
window
and then if we spin round then we have the long back wall
that runs along and then takes us up
to
C one
which is the
cupboards up here
which currently
hold the
boiler
system and
whatever else and then it's
this wall here
that's
not on your plan
because that'll be coming down
to make this all into one big open room
which then will effectively split back into two rooms again a
bedroom and
a kitchen
but make it a lot better